<string name="TA1name">Deekshabhoomi</string>
<string name="TA2name">Ambazari Lake</string>
<string name="TA3name">Zero Mile Stone</string>
<string name="TA4name">Futala Lake</string>
<string name="TA5name">Maharajbagh zoo</string>
<string name="TA6name">Raman Science Centre</string>
<string name="TA7name">Sitabuldi Fort</string>
<string name="TA8name">Tadoba Andhari Tiger Reserve</string>
<string name="TA9name">Central Museum of Nagpur</string>
<string name="TA10name">Kasturchand Park</string>
<string name="TA1Description">Deekshabhoomi is a sacred monument of Navayana Buddhism located where the architect of the Indian Constitution, B. R. Ambedkar, converted to Buddhism with approximately 600,000 followers on Ashok Vijaya Dashami on 14 October 1956.</string>
<string name="TA2Description">Ambazari lake is situated near the Southwest border of Nagpur. It is one of the 11 lakes in Nagpur and is the largest lake in the city. Nag River of Nagpur originates from this lake. This was built in the year 1870, under Bhonsle rule, for supplying water to the city.</string>
<string name="TA3Description">Zero Mile Stone is a monument built by British during Great Trigonometrical Survey of India in 1907 in Nagpur, Maharashtra. The Zero Mile Stone consists of a pillar made up of sandstone and another small stone representing the GTS Standard Bench Mark, and four stucco horses that were added later.</string>
<string name="TA4Description">Futala Lake is one of the lakes in Nagpur in the Indian state of Maharashtra.The lake is spread over 60 acres. Built by Bhosle kings of Nagpur, the lake is known for its coloured fountains. In the evenings the place is illuminated with halogen lights and Tanga ride.</string>
<string name="TA5Description">Maharajbagh zoo is the central zoo of Nagpur, India. The zoo is located in the heart of the city and has been built on the garden of the Bhonsle and Maratha rulers of the city. The zoo comes under the Central Zoo Authority of India and is maintained by the Panjabrao Deshmukh Krishi Vidyapeeth of Nagpur.</string>
<string name="TA6Description">The Raman Science Centre and Raman Planetarium Complex at Nagpur is an interactive science centre affiliated with Mumbai's Nehru Science Centre.</string>
<string name="TA7Description">Sitabuldi Fort, site of the Battle of Sitabuldi in 1817, is located atop a hillock in central Nagpur, Maharashtra, India. The fort was built by Mudhoji II Bhonsle, also known as Appa Sahib Bhosle, of the Kingdom of Nagpur, just before he fought against the British East India Company during the Third Anglo-Maratha War.</string>
<string name="TA8Description">Tadoba Andhari Tiger Reserve is located in Chandrapur district, Maharashtra state, India. It is Maharashtra's oldest and largest National Park. Created in 1995, the area of the Reserve is 625.40 square kilometres.</string>
<string name="TA9Description">Established in 1863, this museum houses historical coins, sculptures, artifacts \& more.</string>
<string name="TA10Description">This sizable urban park is a popular location for events such as exhibitions \& fairs.</string>
<string name="TA1Timings">12:00 PM - 6:00 PM</string>
<string name="TA2Timings">Open 24 hours</string>
<string name="TA3Timings">Open 24 hours</string>
<string name="TA4Timings">Open 24 hours</string>
<string name="TA5Timings">9:30 AM - 7:00 PM\n9:30 AM - 8:00 PM (Sunday)</string>
<string name="TA6Timings">9:30 AM - 6:00 PM</string>
<string name="TA7Timings">Open 24 hours</string>
<string name="TA8Timings">9:00 AM - 5:30 PM</string>
<string name="TA9Timings">10:00 AM - 5:00 PM</string>
<string name="TA10Timings">Open 24 hours</string>